The movie
电影
This is what about
这是怎么回事
I knew it would come to this
我知道这会发生
What you need is a nice big piece of seaweed
您需要的是一块漂亮的海藻
Outside so this is the awesome rolling matting
在外面，这是很棒的滚动消光
Stephen tries
斯蒂芬尝试
I am putting rice
我放米饭
Phone David
给大卫打电话
I usually get a price on the outside
我通常会在外面定价
How much rice am I supposed to use enough
我应该用多少米
I'm putting on the top because it's going to have to roll
我要登顶，因为它必须滚动
Next ingredients go into this machine
接下来的配料进入这台机器
This Green
这个绿色
The Ritz
丽思酒店
Ok don't worry because when I go to that
好吧，别担心，因为当我去那
Enrol
注册
No it's a rolling
不，这是滚动的
Over this and that over there
在那边那边
This is too big
这个太大了
Unique way to do it
独特的方式
Meatpacking work
肉类包装工作
Don't message me this way
不要这样给我发消息
The something went wrong here
这里出了点问题
Oh no
不好了
Yeah you just dig in there
是的，你只是在那儿挖
Call Laurie
致电劳里
Siri
Side of the rough side
一面粗面
Close down
倒闭
Make sure it's not too hot
确保不太热
Temperature
温度
Spread
传播
Of rice over
饭满
Ingredients
配料
Use the roly-poly that's going around it
使用围绕它的roly-poly
Pulling the basket
拉篮
Sushi time we're going to make some maki rolls which is basically the sort of standard roll sushi
寿司时间，我们要做一些寿司卷，基本上是标准寿司卷
This guy right here the perfect for the task
这个家伙在这里很适合完成任务
They all look about the same to find out the strings around one way and a baby runs the other and the key here is to make sure
他们看起来大致相同，以一种方式找出琴弦，然后以另一种方式婴儿奔跑，这里的关键是确保
Read directions
阅读路线
To the flat side up and the strings running away from you like this ok
朝着平坦的一面，琴弦像这样从你身边溜走
Play slightly smoother shiny side on the lorry and then we have a slightly Corsa side here
在卡车上打一点光滑的发亮的一面，然后在这里我们稍微打一点Corsa的一面
If you want to put a smooth side
如果您想放一个光滑的一面
Against the match in a season
一个赛季对抗比赛
Alright a little bit and we're going to add a pinch of sugar
好一点，我们要加一点糖
Dash of rice vinegar
大米醋
The general rule that the rest of the body
一般规则是身体的其余部分
You can't reason it is going to stick to
你不能说它会坚持下去
A really easy trick to avoid that from happening
避免这种情况发生的非常简单的技巧
Tips of your fingers wet while working with the
使用手指时，手指的尖端会变湿
I'm going to the cinema in a rule of thumb is that your race should be to rain stop
我要凭经验去电影院，你的比赛应该是下雨
If you were to build a house out of race
如果你要在竞赛之外盖房子
Play bricks you want one brick two
玩砖头要一砖两
That's about it
就是这样
The only place I wanna leave a gap is
我唯一想留下的地方是
Turn on the top Edge bar furthest away from me
打开离我最远的顶部边缘栏
I remember less is more so don't go Overboard
我记得少就是多，所以不要过分
Bursting at the seams
接缝处破裂
Runaway couple steps
失控的几个步骤
In here
在这里
What does around one third of the way up
大约三分之一的距离会做什么
I do is roll this inward and then
我要做的是向内滚，然后
It's like a wave breaking in the ocean
就像大海中的浪花
I want to pull me
我想拉我
Map towards me as well
也向我映射
Ok so when I come down
好吧，当我下来
Towards me
朝向我
As I make my
当我做我的
Is it going to rain tonight
今晚要下雨吗
Vegetable maki roll
蔬菜卷